We have been to the moon and sent spacecraft to Mars.
我们已登上了月球，并向火星发射了宇宙飞船。
But would you like to stroll on the red planet and examine the rocky surface of Mars close up from all angles?
但你是否愿意在红色星球上漫步，从各个角度近距离观察火星的岩石表面呢？
Well, for those of us who can't afford our own rocket ship, experiences like this are now a virtual step closer, thanks to AR technology.
对于那些买不起自己火箭飞船的人来说，现在这样的体验“实际上”离我们更近了一步，多亏了AR技术。
The letters stand for 'augmented reality', and even if it's not the most beautiful phrase in English, a lot of people in Silicon Valley think it will be the next big thing in tech.
这几个字母代表“增强现实”，即使这不是英语中最美的短语，硅谷的许多人仍认为它将成为科技界的下一个大事件。
AR refers to the process of displaying digital information on top of the physical world using an electronic device.
AR指的是使用电子设备在物质世界上显示数字信息的过程。
The device could be a pair of smart glasses, a tablet or even a humble smartphone.
设备可以是一副智能眼镜、平板电脑，甚至是一部普通的智能手机。
And unlike 'virtual reality', or VR, users can physically move around and explore the digital world, instead of being restricted to a small area.
与“虚拟现实”不同，用户可以四处走动并探索数字世界，而不是被限制在一个小区域内。
This is particularly exciting for businesses.
这对企业来说尤其令人兴奋。
Alex Kipman is the creator of the HoloLens - a headset which allows people to see and interact with holograms.
亚历克斯·基普曼是HoloLens的创造者——这是一种让人们看到全息图并与之互动的头戴设备。
During the 2016 TED Conference he even 'teleported' a hologram of a NASA scientist onto the stage with him, a stage which was transformed into a virtual Martian landscape.
在2016年TED大会上，他甚至“传送”了一位NASA科学家的全息图到舞台上，舞台被改造成了一个虚拟的火星景观。
In time, AR advocates hope it will allow us to interact with a whole world that is enhanced by multimedia provided by very clever computers - transforming not only business, but also fields like healthcare.
AR的支持者希望它最终能使我们与整个世界互动，这个增强版的多媒体世界由非常聪明的计算机所提供——它不仅会改变商业，还能改变医疗等领域。
A doctor could see patients around the world from the comfort of her own home.
医生可以舒适地在自己家中为世界各地的患者看病。
Not everyone is convinced that either the technology or the world at large is ready.
并不是每个人都相信这项技术或整个世界已经准备好了。
Google's pioneering pair of smart glasses, Google Glass, were deemed a "fascinating failure" by the BBC's technology correspondent.
谷歌开创性的智能眼镜Google Glass被BBC的科技记者认为是一个“引人入胜的失败”。
And Kipman himself thinks we still have a long way to go before AR reaches its potential: "We will look back at this decade as being like cavemen in terms of technology," he said.
基普曼本人认为，AR要实现其潜力还有很长的路要走：“未来我们回顾这十年，从科技角度而言我们就像穴居人，”他说。